

OBJECTIVE

I love to seek new knowledge & hunt to learn something new which is unknown to me. It may be new tech things or upcoming world trends which sector or things come up with new scope & feature for us. . We don't know exactly what invention comes after 5-10 or 20 years we have to make preparations for surviving with strange things. I want to take my job as a challenge. I want to leave my comfort zone & try to learn new things.

I want a challenging career to prove myself as a dedicated & dynamic person in the professional environment of an organization.

CONTACT

MOBILE:

01533131638

LINKEDIN:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/sajidul-hasan-bb18231a0/

EMAIL:

Sajidulhasan4@gmail.com

PORTFOLIO:

GitHub - Sajidulhasan9/Portfolio

Address:

H-480/1 Block-C, Khilgaon, Dhaka, 1219

SAJIDUL HASAN

EDUCATION

American International University-Bangladesh (AIUB), Dhaka, Bangladesh

Bachelor of Science (BSc) in Computer Science & Engineering CGPA- 3.19

(Note-142 credit will complete(including current semester)

Major-Information Systems

Dhaka Bigyan College, Dhaka Bangladesh Higher Secondary School Certificate (HSC) in Science GPA- 3.42

Noapur High School, Feni Bangladesh Secondary School Certificate (SSC) in Science GPA- 3.89

SKILLS

Database Management (SQL)

Data Science: Machine Learning

Programming Language (C, C++,JAVA, C#, Python)

Web Development (HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP)

Additional Skills:

Time Management, Leadership Skills, Teamwork, Critical Thinking & problem solving

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Bengali

English

HOBBIES

- Movie
- Song
- Research
- Writing
- Voluntary Work
- Chess
- Cricket

Key Strengths:

- Ability to meet any challenge with confidence.
- Ability to quickly adapt to changes and pick up things easily.
- Fast learner with a Positive attitude.

Experiences:

MR IT SOLUTION LTD.

Computer Operator 01-01-2020 to 31-12-2020

CFS IT LTD.

(Digital Marketing Agency) Founder & Digital Marketer 01-04-2021 to Present

Mukhopotro24.com

(Online News Paper) News Reporter 05-01-2021 to 01-12-2021

EXTRA CURRICULAR ACTIVITES

- Volunteer at UNICEF Bangladesh
- Campus Ambassador at iBOS Limited (A concern of AKIJ Group)
- Volunteer at Bangladesh innovation Forum

PROJECTS

- Library Management System (C# Project)
 https://github.com/Sajidulhasan9/Library-Management-System
- Hospital Management System (Web Technology Project) https://github.com/Sajidulhasan9/Hospital-Management-Sytem
- Online Doctor Appointment (Software Engineering Projects)
 It merges with the information technology field, whereas the
 programming of data processing systems evolved into
 standardized routines and packages of enterprise resource
 planning software.
- Sixty Dome Mosque (Computer Graphics Porjects)
 It makes with OpenGL (OpenGL is a cross-language, crossplatform application programming interface for rendering 2D
 and 3D vector graphics) in Code::Blocks IDE.
 It has many different view including day view, night view, rainy
 view, Moving animation, Handle with keyboard/Mouse
- E-Commerce Website(Make with HTML,CSS)

 https://github.com/Sajidulhasan9/e-commercesite
- Planning of a Shopping Mall(AUTOCAD Project)
 Feature of building
 Floor Plan of building
 Floor pant Design of Basement & Ground

REFERENCES:

- I. DR. MD. ABDULLAH AL JUBAIR
 Assistant Professor and Head-in-charge (UG)
 abdullah@aiub.edu
- II. MD. FARUK ABDULLAH AL SOHAN Lecturer, Computer Science faruk.sohan@aiub.edu
- III. Md. Joynal Abedin
 Assistant Professor, Dept. of Finance
 abedin@aiub.edu